One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Beyond the heavy rain is a rainbow
hageshii ame no mukou kakaru niji wo mita
I'll know the easy answer's a lie
tayasui kotae wa uso dato shiru darou
Vow not to back down to the shouting
dekai koe nanka ni makenai to chikatte
I need you alone to understand tomorrow
anata hitori ni wakatte hoshii ashita
You gave me the time of my life
yume no youna jikan kureta anata
What do I look like? An ANGEL or a DEVIL...
watashi wa dou mieteruno? sorega tenshi ka akuma ka
Beyond the dawn, beyond the dawn
yoake no mukou yoake no mukou
There's so much I want to tell you
hanashitai koto takusan arun da
Filled with love, with love
ai kometa ai kometa
That can't be written down in a letter
tegami ni kakikirenai omoi da
A small hand in search of eternity
eien wo sagashita chiisana tenohira
Wait!
Kuma! Are you okay?
Kuma!
I-I'm okay!
It's nothing!
That's my boy, Kuma!
Your mother's dead...
She should be in heaven by now.
I think...
...she's better off that way.
Hey, Kuma. You're strong.
Endure! Endure and survive!
Shut up-eh!
Hold it right there!
I choose life!
How about you guys?!
"A History Erased!
God Valley of Despair"
God Valley, West Blue
Now, today's prey is released!
The 13 Super Rare Rabbits that we've already
introduced are worth 10,000 points each!
And there are also 150 Rare Rabbits!
Any one-hit kill will earn you
an "Excellent Bonus"!
And we have some fine prizes
for the champion!
Watch, children...
I won't let you win, Garling.
The Manmayers will get the trophy!
Not so fast! Follow the rules!
This is wrong!
Please tell me this is just a nightmare!
Humans should not treat
other humans as toys--
My child!
We're gonna pull off this operation
at any cost!
So, get fired up!
Yeah!
There are 200 World Noble hunters!
The hunt will begin an hour from now!
Now, run!
Marine Headquarters
God Valley?
Why should I go to such a remote island?!
I can't tell you that! But please, Garp!
No!
We're not certain,
but we can't take any chances!
Is it the Celestial Dragons' school trip?
I told you not to poke the Beehive!
You can't screw with them.
That was treasure from Pirate Island.
Of course, they'll come to take it back.
I wonder where the
information leaked from.
You've got plenty of eyes on them,
don't you?
Why are you scared?
Well, we didn't expect...
...Roger would get involved...
Say that part first!
I'm going!
The Rocks Pirates set sail!
Pirate Island of Beehive, New World
Damn! They went ahead of us!
We gotta catch up! Hurry up!
This is a huge deal in the world of pirates!
All right! The game begins now!
Guys! Look at the sea!
There are more Marine ships than I've
ever seen surrounding the island!
Obviously, no one can get off this island,
and the very fact
that such a cruel thing is happening...
...will be erased from history!
A game of murder to remove the natives
from the island for natural resources!
Every last one of about 100,000
Rabbits on the island...
...will be dead in three weeks
when this competition is over!
Can you believe this?!
Are we actually in hell?!
B-But...
If we survive the three weeks,
we'll be free...
That's not gonna happen!
In all previous competitions,
there were no survivors!
What?!
If so, how come they gave us hope?
If you have hope, you run for your lives!
Killing people who sit in despair...
...is no fun for them!
Stop dreaming about
surviving this sick game!
We gotta escape from the game itself!
That's impossible...
St. Garling has already
earned 100,000 points!
Is he targeting high-value Rabbits?!
All right, it came off!
You've got a great jaw!
It's good to have a shark Fish-Man!
Th-Thanks!
I've never been complimented before.
Ginny, how's it going?
This is strange...
I'm sure they got the information.
But neither the pirates nor the Marines
have taken action.
Why?!
What are you doing?
It's obvious, isn't it?!
I'm manipulating information!
The prizes for the competition
are the key to our escape!
The prizes?
One of them is a Devil Fruit
of the strongest class which allows you...
...to transform
into a mythical Azure Dragon!
And the other one!
It enables you to send yourself
and others flying to distant islands!
It's called the Paw-Paw Fruit.
They're both here on the island!
If one of us can eat them,
the dozens of us can get past the Marine blockade and escape this hell!
It's impossible!
The prizes are at the center of the island.
They'll kill us before we find them!
I'm a professional at thieving,
wiretapping, and transmissions!
Two weeks ago, I leaked information
about this island to the outside!
Soon pirates will be flooding the island
in search of treasure
and there will be pandemonium!
But that's not enough
to pull off the operation.
One of us needs to attract the attention
of the Celestial Dragons as a decoy.
A decoy...
I'll do it.
Kuma!
I'm big, so I think
I can survive longer than others.
Besides...
I'd rather not see anyone else die...
Heehaw!
Well said, Kuma!
I won't let anyone kill you!
Let's get off God Valley together!
"Justice"
What's that?!
To the east of the island!
It's the Rocks Pirates!
The Rocks Pirates?! Why?!
Not only them!
Ships of ill-famed pirates
are coming one after another!
We haven't been told about this!
What do they want?!
Shoot!
It's no use, Marines!
Follow me! Rocks Pirates!
Hey wait, Rocks!
When did I become your subordinate?!
You fool!
Oh, Newgate! Not you too!
You're so pathetic, Stussy.
You too, Gloriosa.
It's finders keepers!
Any complaints?
What are you talking about?!
I'll have both.
But they'd be useless to you, Linlin!
They'll be my treasure!
That fool, Rocks,
will surely lose sight of the goal!
Let's check the treasure first!
Stop acting like our leader!
I'll send everyone flying!
I'll just steal what I'm after
and get out of here.
Everyone needs to stop dreaming!
I heard that Roger's on the move, too!
I can't let him--
Calm down, kid!
We'll have the final battle today!
That's the idea here!
We'll settle it once and for all!
The Rocks Pirates have made landfall!
Pirates?!
What are you doing, Marines?!
If anything happens to us,
we will punish you-eh!
Reporting in!
Pirate crews are coming from all directions!
We can't stop them!
How did they know about this?!
This was kept strictly confidential!
We don't know what they want!
Watch out on the western shore!
It's the Roger Pirates!
Do you have any idea how I've felt
this whole year?!
This is going to be a wild one!
Roger!
No first dibs by the captain here!
Let's go, guys!
Pull back the soldiers and have
them guard the Celestial Dragons!
So pathetic.
What was the point of the blockade?!
Let's go, Holy Knights!
Yeah.
We have to get the prizes before them!
We gotta hurry, Kuma!
Okay!
Roger... Rocks...
We might not be able to
hold out any longer.
- Reinforcements arrived!
- What?
Where is he?!
Tell me where Roger is!
We're saved!
Please evacuate immediately!
Yes! We got them!
No one's here, right?
All right... Treasure! Treasure!
Let's open it!
Heehaw!
We did it!
Is this a Devil Fruit?
Yeah! I don't know which is which,
but let's just eat them!
Eat this?
Whoa!
Iva-chan!
Ah!
That was close!
I-Iva-chan?
I'll take that one too!
Eat it, Kuma!
You brat! Give it to me!
Don't think!
Eat it and survive, Kuma!
If even one of us survives...
...we win!
You did it! Go, Kuma!
Iva-chan!
Kuma!
The Buccaneer boy...
Your only options are slavery and death.
They were chosen for you by history itself.
Are you important, Mister?
It doesn't make sense
that you're born important...
And if you're born into slavery,
there's no point to being born at all!
If I've got some kind of power,
just like Nika,
I want to save as many of
these poor people as possible!
Which is why you people
will vanish for good.
Wait, Rocks!
You're in my way, Roger!
This incident would fade into
the dark shadows of history.
Sorbet Kingdom,
South Blue
Garp's heroic tale.
Is that all the information they'll reveal?
The world is as the powerful
want it to be.
This reporter named Morgans is garbage.
We have no idea
what happened to that island after all.
Now,
how long are you gonna keep praying, Kuma?
When I think that there were
still lives I could have saved...
Cut it out!
In all that chaos,
you saved over 500 lives!
He's right, Kumachi!
That was unbelievable!
They all thanked you in tears!
It brought me to tears, too!
But...
Your hands liberated people.
Those are the Hands of Liberation!
The Hands of...
...Liberation...
You're strong.
Endure! Endure and survive!
The Warrior of Liberation will come!
So your family ran a church...
It explains so much about you.
All right, I'm gonna sail out to sea!
To enjoy my freedom!
I'll never forget your face!
No one ever has!
I'll stay here with Kumachi and figure
out what to do with my life, Big Bro!
I like that idea!
Goodbye, my friends!
Now!
Since I'm four years older than you,
I have to feed you!
Huh?
I'm gonna chop firewood!
Ow, ow, ow...
Ginny, are you okay?
Should I chop it with this?
Yeah!
Chop, Kumachi!
All right!
Let's sell them!
Yeah.
No more scavenging or stealing!
Let's earn money and buy food!
Yeah.
Let's do it!
We're sold out!
Yeah.
I'm starving!
What should we eat today?
Whatever you like.
Yay!
Well, then...
You two don't look familiar!
You don't!
You're big! How old are you?
I'm nine.
What?! Nine?!
Mm-hm, mm-hm.
You liar!
- You monster!
- Ouch!
Stop it!
Come on! Don't bully Kumachi!
Ginny!
I'm sorry... Ginny is actually very nice.
What?
- It healed!
- The pain's gone!
Was it magic?!
- That was amazing, Kumachi!
- Awesome!
Kumachi! Kumachi!
Let's eat.
Let's eat!
I want more.
- Here.
- Are you sure?!
Yummy!
Since you eat so much,
we need to work a lot.
Yeah!
Kumachi, when did you become a slave?
When I was four.
Me too!
It's not something to celebrate...
I'm full!
I'm full...!
I'm... full...
Hm? Ginny?
Kumachi!
I'm starving!
What should we eat today?
Whatever you like.
Kumachi...!
What? Don't cry, Ginny!
I'm so happy.
I can't protect anyone again
mata daremo mamorenai no
It's my fault that the voice is fading away
kiekakaru koe wa boku no sei
I don't even have time to look down
utsumuku hima mo nai no
Gravel marks on my palms
tenohira ni tsuku jari no ato
Start moving again, my ship
mata ugokidase boku no fune yo
Though I can't fly in the broad sky
hiroi sora wa tobenai kedo
I can light up the deep sea
fukai umi wa teraseru kara
We
bokura wa
EVERYDAY owarenai
EVERYDAY, can't let this be the end
EVERYDAY makerenai
EVERYDAY, can't be defeated
We have something here to protect
mamoru mono ga koko niwa aru
This may not be what I expected
yosou chigai kamo?
But we can't stop now
tomarenai yo mou
We go on, sharing loneliness
kodoku wo ima wakeai susumu
Don't be afraid
ojikedzukuna yo
I'm not the same person I was that day
ano hi no boku to chigau kara
No one can stand in my way
dare nimo jama dekinai yo
Now, move aside
saa doite
Conquer the world, believe in the future
sekai wo seishite mirai wo shinjite
Count up the nights
ikutsu mono yoru kazoete
What did you see? What did you learn?
nani wo mite nani wo shitte
To realize what was important
taisetsu na koto ni kidzuita no